// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following command is used to create react-js-app ?",
    answer: "npx create-react-app appname",
    options: [
      "npx create-react-app appname",
      "npm install create-react-app",
      "	npx install create-react-app -g",
      "install - l create-react-app"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "In React.js which one of the following is used to create a class for Inheritance ?",
    answer: "Extends",
    options: [
      "Create",
      "Extends",
      "Inherits",
      "Delete"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the default port number in which the application run ?",
    answer: "3000",
    options: [
      "3000",
      "8080",
      "5000",
      "8080"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following valid component return type of React?",
    answer: "1",
    options: [
      "2",
      "5",
      "1",
      "3"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following valid component return type of React?",
    answer: "State & Props",
    options: [
      "State & Props",
      "Services & Components",
      "State & Services",
      "State & Componen"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: " Which of the following is must for the API in React.js ?",
    answer: "renderComponent",
    options: [
      "SetinitialComponent",
      "renderComponent",
      "render",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following is true regarding Babel ?",
    answer: "Both of the above",
    options: [
      "Compiler",
      "Transpilar",
      "Both of the above",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "In React.js, how we can pass the data from one component to another in React.js ?",
    answer: "Props",
    options: [
      "SetState",
      "Render with arguments",
      "Props",
      "PropTypes"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following function is true about changing the state in React.js ?",
    answer: "this.setState",
    options: [
      "this.State{}",
      "this.setState",
      "this.setChangeState",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following method is true about referring parent class in React.js ?",
    answer: "super()",
    options: [
      "self()",
      "inherits()",
      "this()",
      "super()"
    ]
  }
];